A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Scientific Staff Biographical Files FA260
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Silver, Lawrence, 1951-1953 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Simms, Henry S., 1920-1932 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Simms, Samuel, 1922 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Simpson, James C.E., 1933 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Singer, Ira, 1954-1959 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Skupin, Janusz S., 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Slanetz, Charles A., 1927-1930 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Slater, Robert J., 1949-1954 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Smadel, Joseph E., 1934-1954 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Smadel, Joseph E., 1934-1954 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Smillie, Wilson G., 1916-1928, 1937, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Smith, David T., 1923-1925 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Smith, Dorothea Egleston (Mrs. James Farr II), 1919, 1931, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Smith, Emil L., 1940-1941, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Smith, Frederick, 1928-1931, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Smith, Honor Vivian, 1948-1949 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Smith, J. James, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Smith, John (Iain) Maclean, 1953-1954 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Smith, Kenneth M., 1939 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Smith, Margaret H.D., 1946-1953 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Smith, William E., 1942-1945 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Smithburn, Kenneth C., 1930-1949 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Smyly, Henry J., 1919 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Smythe, Carl V., 1930-1946 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Sobotka, Harry, 1924-1926 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Solokoff, Boris, 1922-1944 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Soriano, Victor, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Sotelo, José Roberto, 1954-1958 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Spackman, Darrel H., 1954-1959 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Sparatore, Fabio, 1957-1959 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Spassky, Boris A., 1962-1970 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Spencer, Ernest L., 1932 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Spitznagel, John K., 1952 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Sprague, James M., 1955 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Sprince, Herbert, 1943-1954 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Spring, William C., 1939-1942 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Sprunt, Douglas H., 1929-1930 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Spühler, Otto, 1945-1946 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Stadie, William C., 1918-1922 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Stahmann, Mark A., 1942-1945 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Stall, Bernard George, III, 1949-1956 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Stamm, Guido, 1938-1941 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Steele, J. Murray, 1929-1951 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Steere, Russell Ladd, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Steiger, Robert E., 1932 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Stern, Herbert, 1949-1958 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Stern, Kurt G., 1930-1945, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Stetson, Chandler Alton, Jr., 1947-1959 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Stevens, Henry, 1926-1951 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Stevens, Philip G., 1929 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Stewart, Fred Waldorf, 1926, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Stewart, Harold Julian, 1922-1932, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Stewart, Walter Alexander, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Stiller, Eric Thomas, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Stillman, Edgar, 1913-1926, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Stillman, Ernest G., 1915-1984 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Stock, Charles Chester, 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Stoffel, Wilhelm, 1956-1959 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Stokes, Adrian, 1913 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Stone, Robert Samuel, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Stracher, Alfred, 1956, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Straub, Elmer L., 1923-1925 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Strock, Lester William, 1932-1937 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Strong, Leonell C., 1921-1925 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Strong, Leonell C., 1921-1925 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Stumberg, John Edward, 1931-1933 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Sturm, Ernest, 1922-1955 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Sturman, Martin, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Sullivan, W. James, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Suter, Emanuel W., 1948-1952 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Suzuki, Taizo, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Svensson, Harry, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Syverton, Jerome Theda, 1932-1934, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Tadokoro, T., 1919 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Takahashi, Noboru, 1958-1960 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Tal-Litwinowsky, Chloe, 1948-1952 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Tallan, Harris Herman, 1950-1959 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Tanzer, Radford C., 1930 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Taylor, Dermot B., 1948 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Taylor, Fred A., 1917-1919 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Taylor, Herbert Douglas, 1915-1919 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Taylor, Herbert Douglas, 1915-1919 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Taylor, Marian Sibyl, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Taylor, Walter H., 1918 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Teir, Harald Gustav, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Teixera, Jose de Castro, 1938-1941 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Teng, Chih Chiang, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Teorell, E. Torsten A., 1934-1935 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Terni, Tullio, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Terrell, Edward Eugene, 1931-1934, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- Terry, Benjamin T., 1906-1913 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Terry, Benjamin T., 1906-1913 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Terry, Benjamin T., 1906-1913 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Terry, Benjamin T., 1906-1913 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Tezok, Fethi, 1951-1953 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Thaysen, Jørn Christian Hess, 1951-1954 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Theiler, Hans, 1925 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Theodorpoulos, Demetrios Miltiades, 1953-1956 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Therman, Per Olaf, 1939-1940, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- [not assigned] (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Thjötta, Theodor, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Thoren, J.J., 1957 (Box 31, Folder 11A)
- Thomas, Lewis, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Thomas, Robert M., 1930-1935 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Thompson, Helen, 1946-1948 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Thompson, Robert H.S., 1937 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Thorn, Niels Anker, 1952-1956 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Thornberry, Halbert Houston, 1931-1938 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Thygeson, P., 1937 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Tibbetts, Helena A.M., 1922 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Tilden, Evelyn B., 1916-1933 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Tillett, William Smith, 1922-1949, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Timonen, Kaapo Sakari, 1953-1954 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Tipson, Robert Stuart, 1930-1945 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Todd, Edgar William, 1927-1947 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Toennies, Jan Friedrich, 1935-1939 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Trask, James D., Jr., 1917-1922, 1942, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Traub, Erich, 1932-1955 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Traub, Erich, 1932-1955 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Trautman, Rodes, 1954-1956 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Tribble, Charles Emerson, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Tritsch, George Leopold, 1956-1959 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Tsaltas, Theodore, 1952-1956 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Turner, Joseph Richard, 1914-1915 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Tyrrell, David Arthur John, 1951-1958 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Tytler, William H., 1911 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Uhle, Frederick Charles, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Uhlenhuth, Eduard, 1913-1915, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Uhlenhuth, Eduard, 1913-1915, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Ullstrup, Arnold John, 1934-1937 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Uppal, B.N., 1933 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Uziel, Mayo, 1945-1956 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Van Allen, Chester Montague, 1922-1950 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Vanamee, Parker, 1948-1951 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- van den Berghe, Louis, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Vanden Schrieck, Henry George, 1953-1954 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- van der Hoeven, Bernard Jacob Cornelis, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Vander Scheer, James, 1923-1939 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Van der Schueren, Gerard, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Van der Want, Jan Pieter Hendrik, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- van Leeuwen, W. Storm, 1919-1921 (Box 32, Folder 17A)
- van Ormondt, G., 1935 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Vaubel, Ernst, 1931-1932 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Vedder, Edward B., 1913 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Vidal, Frederick, 1955-1959 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Vinograd-Villchur, Miriam, 1915-1917 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Volkert, Mogens D.H., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Vollmond, Erik Simon, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Wagner, Gorm, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Wagner, Henry G., 1958 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Walker, Duard Lee, 1946-1948 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Walker, Ernest Linwood, 1912-1913 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Wallace, George Barclay (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Wallenius, Gunnar, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Walshe, John Michael, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Walti, Alphonse, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Wannamaker, Lewis William, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Warburg, Bettina, 1929-1930 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Warren, Joel, 1940-1942 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Wasteneys, Hardolph, 1915-1918 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Wasteneys, Hardolph, 1915-1918 (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Watson, Dennis W., 1942 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Watson, Michael Lasell, 1954-1957 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Watson, Robert Fletcher, 1939-1954 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Webster, Leslie Tillotson, 1943-1944, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Webster, Leslie Tillotson, 1943-1944, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Webster, Leslie Tillotson, 1943-1944, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Weisiger, James Richard, 1945-1956 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Weiss, Samuel B., 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Wellhausen, Edwin J., 1936-1937 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Wells, Helen S., 1952 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Welo, Lars Alvin, 1923-1929 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Welsch, Maurice, 1939-1940, 1951-1952 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- West, Clarence Jay, 1912-1920 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Weyer, Elliott Ross, 1927-1932 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- White, Philip Rodney, 1932-1947 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- White, Thomas Nash, Jr., 1929-1931 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Wignall, Ernest E., 1929-1931, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Wikler, Abraham, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Wilbrandt, Walther, 1933, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Wildman, Ernest Atkins, 1915, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Wilska, Alvar Peitari Johanne, 1940-1941 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Wilson, Armine Taylor, 1939-1949 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Wilson, George Wade, 1917-1919, 1935 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Wilson, James, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Winternitz, M.C., 1914-1920 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Wintersteiner, Oskar, 1927, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Wiseman, Bruce Kenneth, 1929-1930 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Wissig, Steven L., 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Witherbee, William D., 1916-1920 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Wittenberg, Jonathan B., 1950 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Wolfrom, Melville L., 1927-1928, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Wolken, Jerome J., 1951-1952 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Wollman, Seymour H., 1948 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Wood, Harrison Frederick, 1947-1955 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Wooley, Janet McCarter, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Worth, Charles Brooke, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Wright, Donald Decker, 1942-1945 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Wright, Francis Howell, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Wright, George Payling, 1925-1930 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Yager, Robert H., 1948 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Yamada, Eichi, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Yamagawa, Makoto, 1917 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Yamakawa, Shitar, 1916 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Yang, Chia-Chih, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Yang, Peter Sushun, 1931-1933 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Yoeli, Meir, 1952-1953 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Zachau, Hans George, 1958, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Zamecnik, Paul C., 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Zervas, Leonidas, 1934-1936 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Ziegler, James E., Jr., 1942 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Zillessen, Frederick Otto, 1926 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Zilversmit, Donald B. (Box 34, Folder 22)